

Dustin Smith

Full Stack Developer

707-280-6500 · dustinsmith1983@gmail.com

Skills

Critical thinking and problem solving

Web Development Skills:

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- MySQL
- Mongoose
- React
- Vue
- Bootstrap
- JQuery

Ability to Work in a Team
Communication Skills
Communication Leadership
Fast Learner
Customer Service Marketing
and Sales
B2B Sales

Profile

Full stack developer having recently completed the Full Stack Web Development Boot Camp from UC Irvine. Having 20+ years in sales experience I decided I wanted to move back into coding. My skill set includes HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, JQuery, MySQL, Mongoose, React, and Vue.

Employment History

Wholesale Sales Account Representative, FrSky RC INC North America, Brea, CA

March 2019 — July 2021

Wholesale Account Representative for Remote control electronics used in both Hobby and Commercial fields. Responsible for managing dealer accounts, being their point of contact for placing orders or any other issues they might have. Responsible for seeking out new dealers and bringing them onboard with the brand.

Online Sales Manager, Adventure RV/Napa Auto Center, Napa, CA

June 2002 — February 2019

This was my family business. I started working here immediately after High School. I started with selling cars. Over the years I took on more responsibility starting with managing all of the dealerships online presence. Eventually moving more into a leadership role at the dealership. Being a family business this required wearing almost every "hat". From acting as a service manager, F&I, handling warranty processing, managing employees ect. I was also responsible for choosing which back end systems, CRM systems, and pretty much any other technology based items that the dealership needed. After about 10 years of being a car dealership we decided to switch focus and while we maintained a small lot of used vehicles we focused primarily on becoming a new RV dealership. I left because my father wanted to retire and I was frustrated with the RV industry. This combined with a desire to move away from Napa led to my choice to not take over the dealership and move in another direction. So we sold the business and I moved to Southern California.

Website project manager, Genacom, Napa, CA

This position was to act as both sales and project manager for web site construction. I was the primary point of contact with the client while being responsible for distributing different aspects of the construction to assorted subcontractors to develop. Then putting those individual pieces together to complete the final product.

Education

High School Diploma, Vintage High School, Napa, CA

September 1998 — June 2002

none, Santa Rosa Junior College, Santa Rosa, CA

August 2002 — December 2003

After High School I started attending college with the intention of getting a degree in computer science. However I was offered a job position at a web development company by a former teacher and with that new position combined with still working part time for my family business this left me with little time to continue school.

Certificate, Full Stack Web Development Boot Camp, UC Irvine, Irvine, CA

September 2021 — March 2022